<resources>
    <string name="title">Psyche Assistant</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="survey">Survey</string>
    <string name="question_of_template">Question %1$d of %2$d</string>
    <string name="not_at_all">Not at all</string>
    <string name="very_much">Very much so</string>
    <string name="selected_score">Selected score: %1$d</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="sum_score">Total score: </string>
    <string name="language">Language: </string>
    <string name="completed">Survey completed!</string>
    <string name="final_score">You scored a total of %1$d on the Mental Fatigue Scale.</string>
    <string name="symptoms">General Symptoms: </string>
    <string name="recommendations">General Recommendations: </string>
    <string name="low_fatigue_symptoms">&#8226; Occasional, mild difficulties with concentration and memory.\n&#8226; Slightly increased sensitivity to stress, but manageable.\n&#8226; Normal functioning in daily activities with minimal impact.</string>
    <string name="low_fatigue_recommendations">&#8226; Be aware of early signs of fatigue but understand that these symptoms are minor.\n&#8226; Ensure to maintain a healthy lifestyle, including regular sleep, exercise, and balanced diet.\n&#8226; Regular relaxation and stress management techniques may help in preventing escalation of symptoms.</string>
    <string name="moderate_fatigue_symptoms">&#8226; Noticeable difficulties in concentration and memory, affecting some daily tasks.\n&#8226; Increased sensitivity to stress, leading to irritability and frustration.\n&#8226; Feeling mentally drained after routine tasks that did not previously cause fatigue.</string>
    <string name="moderate_fatigue_recommendations">&#8226; Consider implementing structured rest periods during the day to alleviate fatigue.\n&#8226; Prioritize tasks and activities to manage energy levels more effectively.\n&#8226; Engage in activities that promote relaxation and reduce stress, such as mindfulness, yoga, or gentle exercise.\n&#8226; It may be beneficial to seek advice from a healthcare professional to manage symptoms.</string>
    <string name="high_fatigue_symptoms">&#8226; Significant concentration and memory problems, making daily tasks challenging.\n&#8226; High sensitivity to stress, leading to frequent irritability, frustration, and possibly mood swings.\n&#8226; Feeling mentally exhausted most of the time, with a noticeable impact on work, social life, and personal relationships.</string>
    <string name="high_fatigue_recommendations">&#8226; Strongly consider seeking medical advice to explore potential underlying causes and appropriate treatments.\n&#8226; Implement regular, substantial rest periods and avoid overexertion.\n&#8226; Cognitive-behavioral strategies might be useful to manage symptoms and improve daily functioning.\n&#8226; It is important to communicate with employers, friends, and family about the fatigue to seek their support and understanding.</string>
    <string name="very_high_fatigue_symptoms">&#8226; Severe concentration and memory issues, significantly impairing the ability to perform everyday tasks.\n&#8226; Extreme sensitivity to stress, leading to frequent emotional outbursts, anxiety, or depression.\n&#8226; Persistent mental exhaustion, often resulting in a reduced ability to engage in social or professional activities.</string>
    <string name="very_high_fatigue_recommendations">&#8226; Immediate consultation with a healthcare professional is critical to address these severe symptoms.\n&#8226; Possible need for medical intervention, including medication and/or therapy.\n&#8226; Consider a comprehensive approach to treatment, which may involve lifestyle changes, mental health support, and possibly occupational therapy.\n&#8226; Ensuring a strong support network of family and friends can help in managing the condition more effectively.\n&#8226; Work on gradual reintroduction to normal activities as the condition improves, under professional guidance.</string>
    <string name="general_recommendations">&#8226; Regular Check-ins: Monitor symptoms regularly to understand if they are getting better or worse.\n&#8226; Healthy Habits: Maintain a routine that includes sufficient sleep, nutritious meals, and physical activity.\n&#8226; Mindfulness and Relaxation: Engage in activities that promote mental relaxation, such as meditation, breathing exercises, or hobbies.\n&#8226; Professional Support: Do not hesitate to seek professional help if symptoms are affecting daily life. Early intervention can prevent further deterioration.</string>
    <string name="low">Low</string>
    <string name="moderate">Moderate</string>
    <string name="high">High</string>
    <string name="very_high">Very high</string>
    <string name="danish">Danish</string>
    <string name="english">English</string>
    <string name="previous_results">Previous Results</string>
    <string name="date">Date</string>
    <string name="score">Score</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
</resources>